You know, that's what you guys always say.
But nothing ever happens.
We won't have any peace
until that Billy leaves us alone!
Look, if you want--
Uh, Ma…
Let me deal with Billy.
I'll handle her, okay?
Ta-da!
What's that?
Since you weren't able
to come to my birthday parties,
I'll just show them to you instead!
This here is from my first birthday!
This here is Jordan, Billy's best friend.
Good buddies!
After that,
we started celebrating
my birthdays at the cemetery.
You know what happened to Mom, right?
She died while giving birth to me.
I'm sorry, Oliver.
I'm sorry that I wasn't there
when you all needed me.
When your mom needed me.
Pa, did you ever love Mom?
You know what, Oliver?
I loved your mother.
It's a shame that I didn't have the chance
to ask for her forgiveness.
I'm sure she can see how sorry you are.
Hug?
Hug. Hug.
- Fist bump!
[OLIVER] Fist bump!
- Boom.
- Bye, Pa!
- Be good, okay?
- Yes!
- Okay, go!
[ENRICO] Take care!
[PETER] To our press,
to our beloved journalists,
our social media influencers,
and reporters,
thank you so much for being here today
as we,
as LoveList,
goes from a regional brand
to a global brand.
- [BLAIRE] Awesome! Whoo!
- [PETER] Thank you.
- [BLAIRE] You may take your seats.
- [PETER] I'm excited. Thank you.
[BLAIRE] And we can
sign the contract now.
[PETER] All right.
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
[APPLAUSE]
[PETER]
So, you believe in online dating?
[BEA] I guess.
That's why I'm using this app.
Is it any good?
I hope I can find
my match.
Bea.
Peter.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
- Mmm, want more?
- [EXHALES SOFTLY]
- Yeah.
- Hmm, yes?
- Yes, sure.
- Yes? Okay.
- Game.
- I'll take care of it.
- [GLASS CLINKING]
- [GIGGLES]
[PETER] You're the boss.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Wait for me.
- Mm-hmm.
- [LAUGHS]
- [ALCOHOL SLOSHING]
[SETS BOTTLE DOWN]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] Here we go.
[PETER SLURRING] Yes, baby.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARJ] Admit it, girls.
Sir Peter is a cutie, isn't he?
- Hmm?
- He's married, Marj.
[MARJ] I just find him cute, that's all.
- Just have a drink.
- Oh, yes.
[RAIN] Hey, why don't you ask
if she received the flowers?
Don't rush it. Just let it be.
We can wait.
[RAIN] Maybe she didn't get them.
- Just don't worry about it.
- Sure, whatever.
- These are ready.
- You do it.
- Bring the drinks to them.
- Fine.
[ALCOHOL SLOSHING]
[BOTTLE THUDS]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
- Come on, serve the drinks.
- Yeah, yeah.
[RAIN] She's coming.
- Robbie, hi!
- Hi.
- Hi, Val.
- Hey… [CHUCKLES] Hi.
Um…
So, I received the flowers and the…
the letter.
- Yes, yes.
- [CHUCKLES] Yeah. Um…
And I just want to say thank you
'cause, you know, it's so sweet.
And… [INHALES DEEPLY]
Yeah. Um…
I don't want to hurt your feelings, but…
You know, I just have to say this now.
I can only offer friendship
and nothing more than that.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah.
Yeah. [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Already friend-zoned…
Uh-- [STAMMERS]
But you know,
I had no plans to lead you on
in the first place.
That's why I'm giving you
this honest response.
So… yeah.
You're welcome!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Bye!
[LOUD THWACK]
Well, that's that.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
"So, you're welcome." All right then.
Take a shot.
- I'll take a shot.
- Shot.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Another toast.
To the right choices we made
and the ones we'll make.
Cheers, guys.
[EVERYONE]
Cheers!
- More!
- Cheers!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Yeah.
Because I knew investing in LoveList
was the right decision.
Well, I'm just waiting for my mom to hear
that LoveList is going global.
And by that time,
all the decisions I made…
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I know my mom's…
She's wrong.
And she'll realize that soon enough.
Okay?
Well,
I just hope things get better
between you and your mom.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You see?
That's why you're the best
amongst all my decisions, babe.
- [TONI SQUEALS]
- Hey.
Have some respect for the singles around.
- Damn right!
- [TONI GIGGLES]
Well… Cheers.
- Aww…
- Ah, wait.
Billy, let me go ahead
and apologize, okay?
[BILLY] Hmm?
[YANI] Since LoveList is going global now,
the workload will surely double
or even triple.
So, can I spend some time alone with Toni?
Just two weeks' leave would do.
Hmm? Two weeks?
- [YANI] Just two weeks.
- Why two weeks?
Uh…
My love, you explain.
[TONI CLEARING THROAT]
[RALPH] Oh.
- [GLASS THUDS]
- [TONI GIGGLING]
"You're cordially invited
to the wedding of Toni and Yani."
[CHARM] The wedding's really happening?
- It's really happening?
- What? Really?
Whoa! It's next month!
- [BILLY] Congrats!
- It's finally happening!
- [SQUEALING]
- [CLAPPING]
- Congrats!
- Thank you, girls! Thank you!
Aw, finally!
I so love happy endings! [GIGGLES]
Congrats, guys!
- It's really happening, huh?
- Whew, finally!
- Happy wedding!
- Oh my God!
- [SOFT LAUGH]
- Okay.
Here.
Bottoms up!
- Mm-hmm.
- [PETER CHUCKLING]
- Mmm?
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh.
- It's good, right?
Now…
[CHUCKLES]
- Are you ready?
- Yes, I am.
Why are you so beautiful?
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
- That whisky…
- Hmm?
It's strong.
Strong?
Uh… no, it's not.
You're just a lightweight.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SHUTTER CLICKING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
["TRAFFIC" PLAYING]
♪ It's such a waste of time
Being stuck in traffic ♪
♪ It's so damn frustrating ♪
♪ What if this never happens again? ♪
♪ My body aches from sitting for hours ♪
♪ I'm starting to hesitate ♪
♪ What if you suddenly go home? ♪
♪ Baby, I'm sorry, I'm still dreaming ♪
♪ I can't blame this on anyone ♪
♪ If only I could fly over EDSA
Then I wouldn't have to wait ♪
♪ Why is it like that? ♪
♪ So many are rushing to get ahead ♪
♪ Why does it feel so far
When you're right there? ♪
♪ I'm afraid I won't catch up
If the world stops ♪
♪ I'm willing to try
Even if I get stuck in traffic ♪
♪ What number am I in line? ♪
- [CHEERING]
- [CLAPPING]
♪ Maybe I can get ahead ♪
♪ I promise I won't back down
From your suitor ♪
♪ Baby, I'm sorry, I'm still dreaming ♪
♪ I can't blame this on anyone ♪
♪ If only I could fly over EDSA
Then I wouldn't have to wait ♪
♪ Why is it like that? ♪
Do you think she still likes Boss Jordan?
[RAIN] Yeah.
It's okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Robbie.
Oh, Val.
No hard feelings, okay?
Absolutely.
No hard feelings, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
I'll just put this inside.
Okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh…
Come on.
Why don't you give him a chance?
[SCOFFS]
I can ask you the same thing.
Why don't you give yourself a chance?
What do you mean?
You wrote this, right?
Yeah.
- But…
- I knew it.
But what's written there is true.
Yeah.
But you didn't write this
to express Robbie's feelings for me.
You wrote it to express your feelings…
for someone else.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jordan.
We were together for
almost a year.
And I knew.
I always knew it was Billy.
And I was in denial because…
I don't know.
Maybe I was hoping eventually,
you'll learn to love me more
than you love her.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But…
But don't worry.
I know we're just friends.
But I don't get it.
What's holding you back?
Why can't you just be honest with her?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I mean, I'm telling you this
as your friend.
Do yourself a favor and talk to Billy.
And tell her how much you love her.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GLASS CLINKS]
- Uh, babe?
- I need to use the restroom.
- Mm.
Okay.
Mm.
What's wrong?
[EXHALES]
Okay.
I know I wanted Ralph to learn
to stand up to his mother.
But now that he has,
I feel guilty.
I feel like I ruined their relationship.
Don't say that.
You did nothing wrong.
Billy, that's what
I've been telling myself.
But I still feel guilty anyway.
But, as they say,
a parent could never turn
their back on their child.
But a child could turn
their back on their parent.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you believe that?
Well, it's what I did.
But things have changed.
You allowed Oliver to talk to his father.
Oliver is a different story.
I can't say no to that kid.
[SIGHS]
But I hope…
I really hope
Ralph doesn't ignore his mother forever.
I want them to patch things up.
I really do.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mm-hmm!
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Thank you.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
- Auntie.
- Hi, Billy.
- Mm.
- Mwah!
Uh, your brother wanted you to see this.
Oh, wow.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
YOU'RE THE BEST SISTER IN THE WORLD
I secretly recorded this too,
so I could show it to you.
Here.
Your father said
he'll never leave you guys again.
Have you made your decision, Billy?
I gave Oliver what he wanted.
But that's it.
Billy, this is going to hurt him.
Is it just Oliver who will get hurt?
Or you too?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you still love him?
Even though he lied to you?
[MUSIC TURNS POIGNANT]
He promised he won't leave us anymore?
That is exactly what I'm trying to avoid.
Getting Oliver's hopes up
only for him to be
left behind all over again.
He needs to walk away.
From you and Oliver.
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm really sorry.
[MARIELA SCREAMING]
M-Ma?
Ma.
Ma?
I'm here, Ma.
You're having a bad dream.
Wake up.
Are you okay?
- Hmm?
- As long as your father
and his mistress are together
with that Billy and her little brother,
those bastard children…
I will never be okay.
Never.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
It's already more than enough that
you were given the chance
to spend time with Oliver.
Billy, please.
I need more time with him.
One more week. It's better this way
than to drag this out.
Billy is going down.
Mark my words.
I'll tell your wife about it.
Hack into LoveLine.
Once LoveList is completely ruined,
that's when I'll delete
all the pictures.
Okay?
There has been a huge spike
in the number of subscribers.
[BLAIRE] Oh, hi, Sir Fab!
What a surprise!
I'd like to take a look at
the LoveLine area.
- May I?
- Yes, you may.
Feel at home.
Sorry, chief. Sir Peter's here.
Huh? You didn't tell me
he was coming today.
He just suddenly arrived.
I thought you were expecting him.
Hi!
- [BILLY] Peter.
- [PETER] Hi!
Sorry, I wasn't expecting you.
[PETER] Hi.